<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>esp3j0</title>
        <link>https://esp3j0.github.io/</link>
        <description>This is my cool site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-CN</language><managingEditor>esp3j0@outlook.com (esp3j0)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>esp3j0@outlook.com (esp3j0)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 09:45:47 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://esp3j0.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>对于神经网络中张量中各种维度的理解</title>
    <link>https://esp3j0.github.io/posts/tensor/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 09:45:47 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>esp3j0</author>
    <guid>https://esp3j0.github.io/posts/tensor/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[引言 咱们高中，大学上线代课程的时候都会接触到一个词&ndash;向量&ndash;，向量这个东西有个被称为维度的属性。 平面中的一个点，可以用]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>WindowsRegister</title>
    <link>https://esp3j0.github.io/posts/windowsregister/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 14:18:12 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>esp3j0</author>
    <guid>https://esp3j0.github.io/posts/windowsregister/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Windows Registry The simple definition of windows registry The Windows Registry is a hierarchical database that stores low-level settings for the Microsoft Windows operating system and for applications that opt to use the registry. The kernel, device drivers, services, Security Accounts Manager, and user interfaces can all use the registry.
Originally,When intruduced with win3.1,registry primarily stored configuration information for COM-based components. Windows 95 and Windows NT extended its use to rationalize and centralize the information in the profusion of INI files, which held the configurations for individual programs, and were stored at various locations.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>HowToLearn</title>
    <link>https://esp3j0.github.io/posts/howtolearn/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 14:13:02 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>esp3j0</author>
    <guid>https://esp3j0.github.io/posts/howtolearn/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[HowToLearn preface Have you ever paly Minecraft or other games.When you are palying them，you must have one sence that your time fly.We paly them with our all attentions, and never tired.In my opinion,if we know the underlying logic,learning skills is something similar to playing games which is interestng and appealing.
The way to achieve real world goals is similar to mincraft crafting recipes.Everyone has its specific achieving goals methods.As a result.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
